<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>🗣️ English on Eitan&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 🗣️ English on Eitan&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:28:23 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lesson7: Substantive verb</title>
      <link>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson7_substantive_verb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:28:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson7_substantive_verb/</guid>
      <description>In English, when the predicate is not a verb, the verb &amp;rsquo;to be&amp;rsquo;, commonly called the substantive verb,is used to connect the predicate with its subject. This verb has no equivalent in Maori, but the relation of subject to predicate is indicated by the use of certain particles and by the relative position of the different words in the sentence. Some substantive verbs Example: come read go watch play and so on When using substantive verbs, you need to pay attention to the verb tense present tense He comes from Shenyang. present continuous tense She is reading story books. simple past tense They went to America yesterday. present perfect tense We have watched the game for three times. future tense My mother will fly back to china next month. The negative form of the substantive verb When we use the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson6: The Reflexive Pronouns</title>
      <link>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson6_the_reflexive_pronouns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:08:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson6_the_reflexive_pronouns/</guid>
      <description>Reflexive pronouns are pronouns that reflect back to the subject, but how do they work, and what are some examples? Below, we explain what reflexive pronouns are and how to use them correctly. What are reflexive pronouns? Reflexive pronouns are words ending in -self or -selves that are used when the subject and the object of a sentence are the same (e.g., I believe in myself). They can act as either objects or indirect objects. The nine English reflexive pronouns are myself, yourself, himself, herself, oneself, itself, ourselves, yourselves, and themselves. Grammatical terms might seem complicated and a bit arbitrary when you first hear them, but they really aren’t, once you get to know them. The term reflexive is a good example. Through Latin, reflexive is related to reflect; this is useful to remember</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson5: Possessive Pronouns and Possessive Adjectives</title>
      <link>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson5_possessive_pronouns_and_possessive_adjectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 22:30:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson5_possessive_pronouns_and_possessive_adjectives/</guid>
      <description>As their names imply, both possessive adjectives and possessive pronouns show ownership. The independent possessive pronouns are mine, ours, yours, his, hers, its, and theirs. The possessive adjectives, also called possessive determiners, are my, our, your, his, her, its, and their. We break down each type and offer examples of their usage below. Independent possessive pronouns Possessive pronouns are a type of possessive noun. Also called absolute possessive pronouns, possessive pronouns simplify constructions that show possession of a noun by replacing it—in other words, independent possessive pronouns must stand alone and be used without a noun. To understand how possessive pronouns can make things simpler and clearer, first take a look at this example of a sentence that does not use a possessive pronoun: Raúl’s peace lilies were healthier than my</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson4: Nominative and accusative forms of pronouns</title>
      <link>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson4_nominative_and_accusative_forms_of_pronouns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 20:48:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson4_nominative_and_accusative_forms_of_pronouns/</guid>
      <description>We use pronouns every day. in fact, even if you don&amp;rsquo;t know what pronouns are, you use them and in this sentence alone, we&amp;rsquo;ve now used pronouns four times. Pronouns are words (or phrases) you substitute for nouns when your reader or listener already knows which noun you&amp;rsquo;re referring to. For example, you might say, &amp;ldquo;i have a dog.She&amp;rsquo;s brown and white.&amp;rdquo; There&amp;rsquo;s no need to clarify that you&amp;rsquo;re describing your dog in the second sentence because you already mentioned her in the first. By using the pronoun she, you can avoid the annoying repetition of the dog. Pronouns do a whole lot more than helping us avoid repetitiveness. They provide context, make your sentences&amp;rsquo; meanings clearer, and shape how we perceive people and things. Read on to learn about the different ways we use pronouns and how to use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson3: The negative form of the verb &#39;to be&#39;</title>
      <link>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson3_the_negative_form_of_the_verb_to_be/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 20:56:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson3_the_negative_form_of_the_verb_to_be/</guid>
      <description>The negative form of the verb &amp;rsquo;to be&amp;rsquo; is &amp;ldquo;is not&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;are not&amp;rdquo;. To form a sentence, it needs to add &amp;ldquo;not&amp;rdquo; after the verb. For example: I am not a teacher. The nagative form of the verb &amp;ldquo;to be&amp;rdquo; verb &amp;ldquo;to be&amp;rdquo; The negative form am am not is isn&amp;rsquo;s are aren&amp;rsquo;t was wasn&amp;rsquo;t were weren&amp;rsquo;t Example Simple Present tense form The man isn&#39;t back. I am not back. They aren&#39;t back. Simple Past tense form He wasn&#39;t back. They weren&#39;t back. The Question and Answer of Sentence Example 1 Q: Is he a teacher? A: Yes, he is. / No, he isn&#39;t. Example 2 Q: Are you a teacher? A: Yes, i am. / No, i am not. Example 3 Q: Were they teachers? A: Yes, they were. / No, they weren&#39;t. More Examples Question: Is he a</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson2: The Verb &#39;To Be&#39;</title>
      <link>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson2_the_verb_to_be/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:28:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson2_the_verb_to_be/</guid>
      <description>The verb &amp;rsquo;to be&amp;rsquo; indicates a state of being or existence. &amp;lsquo;To be&amp;rsquo; is an irregular verb. There are eight forms of the verb to be: 1. Present: am、is、are Example: I am a student. She is a teacher. They are the audience. They are teachers. 2. Simple past: was、were Example He was back. They were back. He was a teacher before 3. Infinitive: be infinitive is a verbal consisting of the word to plus a verb (in its simplest &amp;ldquo;stem&amp;rdquo; form) and functioning as a noun, adjective, or adverb. The term verbal indicates that an infinitive, like the other two kinds of verbals, is based on a verb and therefore expresses action or state of being. Example We need to win. 4. Present participle: being</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson1: The basic sentence patterns</title>
      <link>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson1_the_basic_sentence_patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 23:41:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://EitanWong.github.io/en/posts/english/lesson1_the_basic_sentence_patterns/</guid>
      <description>English is an international language, and being proficient in it allows individuals to communicate effectively with English speakers worldwide. In English, there are five basic sentence patterns. Patterns 1: Subject + Verb Example: Sentence: The universe remains. Note: &amp;lsquo;The universe&amp;rsquo; is the subject of the action of this sentence, certainly, it&amp;rsquo;s the subject of this sentence &amp;lsquo;Remains&amp;rsquo; is the action of this sentence, so it&amp;rsquo;s the verb of this sentence Patterns 2: Subject + Linking Verb + Predicative Example: Sentence: The food is delicious. Note: What is a sentence subject? sentence subject is the subject of the action in the sentence. In English, use a Linking verb to link the subject and Predicative, so is is a Linking Verb. Predicative is relating to or occurring within the predicate of a sentence. Predicate is the part of a sentence that gives</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
